

younes.khoubaz@gmail.com

m Date of birth 06/08/2002

% younes-khoubaz.netlify.app

♥ Kénitra

U +212 687 749447

Single Single

${f A}$ Languages

English

Advanced

French

Advanced

German

■ B1

Arabic

Fluent



Soft Skills

Collaboration

Time Management

Fast learning

Reliabality



Interests

Reading

Music

Internet

Gaming

Summary

I am a highly motivated Full Stack Developer with a bachelor degree specializing in computer science and information technology. I have experience working on diverse software projects including administrative apps as well as user-oriented platforms. Skilled in .NET Core and React.

Education

From 2023 to 2024

Bachelor's in mathematics and computer science

Faculty of science University of Ibn-Tofail

From 2020 to 2022

University diploma of technology (DUT)

Ecole Supérieur de Technologie University of Ibn Tofail

Computer engineering

2020 Baccalaureate

GROUPE SCOLAIRE AL MAJD AL ASSIL Kénitra

- Physics and chemistry sciences
- Excellency

Experience

From April 2024 to June 2024 Development of an online courses platform

Faculty of Science, Ibn-Tofail University / Kénitra

A platform to enroll in online courses, download course

materials, track progress and take quizzes.

From October 2023 to March 2024 Internship - Business travel validation system

CITIC Dicastal /Kénitra (Free Zone)

An administrative application that authorizes business travel requests through several levels of validation.

From April 2022 to June 2022 An online platform that manages final year projects

Ecole Supérieur de Technologie / Kénitra

A platform for managing graduation projects between

students and teachers.

From April 2022 to June 2022 Internship - Development of a management system

The Court of Appeals / Kénitra

A system for managing human and material resources at the Court of Appeal of Kénitra.

Technical Skills

Programming languages

C#, Java, HTML5, CSS, Javascript, SQL

Frameworks & Tools

.NET Web Api, React JS, Git, Azure

Information Systems

UML, Merise